will be like material i come
be able to use Eh But I will try
film a few clips anyway and cut
together into something so when I
is coming
home so that I have with me both lre and
a Canon g7x because my leger has one
Tendency to want to break When I am
abroad and and then of course it charges
to them then and that's kind of all I have
not packed all hygiene items as type
eh toothbrush and d and stuff for that
I will want to use until
Sunday but otherwise I think I have
most of it actually so I hope you
enjoyed this video you see mine
suitcase or How the hell am I supposed to know
close this and I would like to do
one more video before I leave on Sunday
Eh and then I have an idea that I should
vlogging on William student to mine